Take a deep breath in.
And exhale.
Inhale.
Notice the beat of your heart.
The rhythm of life.
You hold the power
to create all that you desire.
Out of nothing.
You okay? Yeah.
What do you see?
What do you feel?
Remember that there's
great power within you.
And that power will guide you
on your journey.
Let me see the gun.
Is it loaded?
I suggest you load it.
Today is a beautiful day of opportunity.
I am exactly where I need to be.
I open myself to the universe and trust in
the unfolding of my life.
This day will bring you peace and
an opportunity for success.
Track your buddies.
Feel this moment.
Have a beautiful rest of your day.
You have found your buddy.
Don't say anything unless you have to, ok?
- This is my cousin.
- Cousin?
Oh no. This is my other cousin.
- Have you done this before?
- Sat in a car for two hours?
Yeah.
Ali, Matthew. Stay here.
Just put the watches in the briefcase, ok?
Hey. What's the problem?
Hands on your head.
- You carrying your gun?
- In the car.
- Get in
- What?
Get in the trunks. Masoud
- Where's your phone?
- In the car.
What's the pin?
1324.
There's water in the trunk.
Six diamonds, eight carats each.
- Fake?
- Get up!
Ready?
Just for safety. I see your weapon.
- What is this?
- It was my dad's gun.
Oh, really?
Who was with that?
John Wayne.
Take this.
You bring it straight back.
No stopping.
- What did I say?
- No stopping.
Fuckin' disrespectful.
Have you seen my keys?
I'm late.
Hey. Can I get a little privacy?
If you're going to take a dump,
then lock the door.
I'm peeing.
You peed. Sitting down. Now.
Best three minutes of my day.
Jesus, that's sexy.
405. The 101 westbound is clear now
between Echo Park Avenue and 1000 Oaks.
Not too bad through downtown,
but it does get heavy.
WTF?
That's your fuckin' house,
Ben. As you can see,
my partner is parked across
the street from your home.
It's just an insurance plan policy.
Same as the jewels you're carrying.
Also covered by insurance.
So let's not do anything stupid,
understand?
When I say go, slowly remove your gun,
both the phones and
throw them into my car.
Clear?
Go.
Slowly. Stay there.
Do not move.
Ben, get out.
Kneel down.
Back to the car.
Eyes forward.
Personally, I wouldn't die
for an insurance company.
Just take it and go.
No, Ben. I want the real
diamonds in the papers now.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Want to get you home to Saraya, Ben.
Help me do that.
Where are they?
- My ankle.
- Which one?
- Left.
- Slowly move them.
Come on, Ben.
Get out.
Let's go. Fuckin' move.
Kneel down.
Here. I'm betting you didn't
back up your photos.
Fuck
Wow. Well, you have a very unique eye.
And your beautiful home here
is a real tribute
to all of your achievements.
What we offer you is the
highest level of protection
for all of these things that
you care so much about.
Protection?
Come here.
What does this look like?
- A thermostat.
- Fingerprint activation.
All, me and my daughter
have to do is touch it.
Boom. Opens in a heartbeat.
Oh. Okay. Never seen that before.
Panic safe.
One in every single room.
Well, that's not going to
lower your insurance premiums,
but I'm certain it must make you feel better.
It fucking well does.
I had two buddies last year,
had home invaders while they were in bed.
- You ever shoot one?
- A home invader?
No. A Glock?
No, that's not exactly my line of work.
You're gonna like it.
- No, no, no.
- It's gonna be good.
- No.
- Here we go. You ready?
Hey, Ramon, could you please move?
Gracias.
I'm probably gonna hit him, you know.
No, no, no. You're not gonna hit him.
He gets out of the way all the time.
All right, I'll take that.
And you take this.
And if you hit one of those bottles,
I'll sign your policy right now.
- Okay?
- Here you go.
Just go ahead and point.
There you go.
All you do is relax
and you just squeeze
when you're ready, okay?
Oh, God.
Well, you didn't hit Ramon.
That's good.
That's good news.
There you go. All right,
Next up.
This needs to be on the policy as it is.
Definitely appreciated.
Since I bought it,
I've only seen that inside a museum.
Cost me $6.2 million.
But we both know contemporary black art
is only going in one direction, right?
Listen, we got a lot
of stuff to go through.
We got a lot of high tech stuff in here.
What makes us different is
that we also protect your privacy.
For example, we also have cyber liability.
Do you remember the admission
scandal of a few years back?
I do, yeah.
Yeah. Well, none of our
clients were named in that.
And, hello, we also will cover
your daughter's possessions
as she goes off to college.
That's my fiance, Adrienne.
Lovely to meet you, Adrienne.
We were just about to talk about
your coverage for your wedding.
Sounds like it's a beautiful venue.
Are you gonna be long, Daddy?
No, we're totally done here.
I knew that it was.
♪ Those were the best days of my life. ♪
Well, well, well. Right next to the 101.
Oh, don't fuckin' start on that, Lou.
Jesus Christ. You ever
going to swap out that bucket?
There's nothing wrong with that bucket.
It's maturing like a fine wine.
- Is it?
- Yeah,
it's depressing is what it is, man.
I just. I can't understand why you
want to look so fuckin' poor.
That ain't what poor looks like.
What do you. What do you care so much for?
Because I got to be
seen riding in it with you.
Detective Buddha.
What do we got here?
Round the back.
Courier got hit
carrying 3 mil worth of
stones from downtown.
He just left these behind, Ben.
But he somehow knew these were fakes so,
I don't know.
We don't know.
Okay? What else can you tell us, Ben?
He knews my wife's name.
And how would he know that?
How the fuck should I know, huh?
Why are you asking me all this shit?
Because, Ben, the one that you
carry in nearly 3 million stones
is the day you get hit.
I mean, that's a little
bit of a coincidence, no?
Well, I didn't give him any information,
if that's what you're asking. Okay,
this, you know, this is victim
blaming what you're doing.
- Oh, I'm victim blaming?
- Yes.
Is that what I'm doing?
Did he take your phones?
Yeah, he did, but he gave them back.
Your cousin says you shot at him.
Your gun fuckin' misfired.
He had a gun? Yeah.
Why didn't he shoot you?
You'll have to ask him.
I told you, don't start on that.
- Start on what?
- That Lone Ranger shit.
It's his mo, man.
What do you mean, his mo?
The MO and not leaving clues behind.
He knows exactly what
they're transporting went.
he cuts the camera line in advance,
there's no violence.
- He's in and out in seconds.
- Okay.
He disappears or right next to the 101.
- Come on, he's got rules.
- Rules?
- He's got rules?
- Yeah. And he sticks to him.
Yeah. There's gonna be another
one we eat for, isn't it?
Come on, dude.
What's going on with you?
The lieutenant says I should
look into a change of partner.
Says if I stick with you,
I'll end up languishing.
Did he? Yep.
What you say?
I told him I didn't want to do that.
Thanks.
But this lone wolf obsession of yours,
it ain't winning us any friends.
It's the same guy and I know it.
Well, you better be fuckin' right, Lou.
Cause I need to step up, man,
and. And soon.
So how'd it go?
Did he show you his weapons?
Not all of them. I hope
It went good.
Did you close?
Yeah. Basically he just, you
know, wants to look over the quote
guys. Like a gazillionaire.
He's got time for that.
Hey, I guess that's how you stay
rich,
right? Well, sure. You nailed it,
Phil. Yeah. Any word on the meeting?
What meeting would that be?
The partners meeting.
The one to finalize
my partnership.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah. I know, I just got to get
the senior team around the same table.
But Mark is just back from
Maui, so let me chase it up.
Yeah, but that's what you said
before he left.
Yeah, well, I'm not in charge of
calendars, Sharon, so.
Well, can we not?
So how'd it go?
There was an incident.
Police?
Yeah, I just. Some kids.
You know, it's nearly went...
I don't know
- You believe in omens.
- Fuckin' omens?
You got shook up, that's all.
This and the next one in Santa Barbara.
You'll have had a good year.
You have a good year too.
And I'm taking all the risk.
You're just selling it.
Something bothering you?
It's just a Santa Barbara job, you know, I.
It doesn't feel right.
It's a lot of money to leave
on the table, champ.
I'll have a buyer waiting.
I don't. It's happening
in the middle of the day,
but we're going straight
in through the front doors.
No way of knowing how
many people be in the car.
Someone could get hurt.
You got something
else in mind?
Yeah, working on something.
Well, good. Now look,
go spend some money.
Get laid.
Relax.
See you later.
You know who this is?
Jonathan.
What happened to Sarah?
Sarah's not well tonight, sweetie.
She said she messaged you.
Okay.
So what do you like to do?
I don't know. Just normal stuff, I guess.
That sounds nice.
Are you an eye contact
or no eye contact guy?
Good morning.
May this day be a
clean slate for your mind,
for your actions
and for your thoughts.
May this day bring.
Before we begin, it is
my pleasure to introduce
the latest member of our valuation team,
Madeline Adcock. Along with Sharon,
Madeline's going to focus on
high net worth residential.
I'm sure we will all make her feel welcome.
Thanks. Thrilled to be here, guys.
Okay, new business.
Sharon just valued one of
the wealthiest estates in all of California
and what is likely to be the most expensive
wedding we have ever insured.
What's the good word for
Monroe, Sharon?
It is promising.
Okay, well, promising is good,
but closed is better.
Next up is Phil.
- What do you got?
- Yeah,
Something fishy on the claim side.
Seven figure claim from a jeweler.
Sammy Kassem, Courrier gets robbed.
The one day in years, if ever he's
transporting 3 million diamonds.
Big coincidence, right? Big coincidence.
Sharon, think maybe you could work your
charms with one of our friends in blue?
Get him to polygraph to vendor
This week, I was planning a follow up
with Monroe, so...
It's a seven figure claim.
Okay, how about we have Madeline
take over the follow up with Monroe?
- You know, fresh face, fresh approach.
- Good idea, Phil.
Yeah, I'd be happy to
take it over if that's okay with you.
Yeah, sure. Okay. Next international.
Sammy, you can see how this looks, right?
No, I. I don't. No.
Okay. What is this? Fat Cop. Bad Cop.
When do you think I started this business?
I opened my store 27 years ago
and I got two other stores.
Why in the world would that shit.
Calm down.
Did. Did. Did you call him to tell him
when to expect the courier?
No, I emailed.
So now what you got to ask yourself is
how does he know who's emailed to hack?
And how could he know
who's intending to transport
something before they transport it?
Same as last time.
Email, calendar, Facebook,
WhatsApp. Instagram
- No Snapchat? Tik Tok?
- She's too old for that.
There's a job up in Santa Barbara.
My guy has laid it all out, but he's not
doing it.
Why ain't he doing it?
He's lost his nerve.
I've seen it before.
He thinks someone could get hurt.
My dad always said
you gotta break a few eggs, so.
Oh, you're not your dad.
God rest his soul.
You might not have the stomach
for some of the things he did.
But if you want a chance
to find out, this is it.
You think you can handle it?
Vermont Narcissia to 11315 South Niga. All units
responding to Code 3 to Vermont NARA 11315
South Dakota
Multiple calls. Male, white, long
brown hair, 28 years. With backpack.
Man. Why'd you stop so suddenly?
I stopped. There's nothing sudden
about it. Red light. You okay?
No, I'm not okay.
I'm late and this is my boss's car.
I just. Can I. I need to get
your insurance information.
Yeah, listen, why don't take this
and then that should cover the damage.
We don't have to worry about
the whole insurance.
What? You just have this wad of cash
you want to pay to not have the hassle?
I don't.
I'm. I'm trying to help
you out. You crashing to me.
I. I appreciate that,
But I. I have to go through
the proper channels.
Otherwise I'm going to get fired.
Let me get a pen.
Yeah, right.
Thousands of dollars in your pocket.
Okay. Sorry.
- There you go.
- Okay.
You got. You got kids?
- What?
- It's a car seat.
Oh, no, no, God.
They're. It's my boss's car.
All right, Yeah,
She's got a pair of twins.
They're pieces of shit.
I don't have kids either.
Okay.
I guess someone will be in touch.
- I don't know how this works.
- Yeah. See you later.
Excuse me. I guess you're the insurance lady.
- And I guess you're the detective man.
- Yeah.
Sharon Combs.
Thanks for meeting with me.
- Sure.
- Want one of these?
Oh, no, thanks. I'm good.
You don't like smoothies?
I don't even like to say the word
smoothie.
So you got something
for me on the Kasem case?
Actually, we were hoping you would consider
polygraphing Kassem and the Courier.
Why? So you could deny his
insurance claim?
He paid his premiums.
What do you want to do?
You want to screw him in return?
It's a nice job you got there, Sharon.
- Yeah,
- Nice.
And how's public service
working out for you?
All you hoped it would be?
I mean, you do make
the world a safer place.
So I guess that's job
satisfaction for you, huh?
At least I'm not screwing
the people I'm paid to protect.
I'm not screwing over anybody.
What we provide is what people want
most in the world. After wealth,
- Wouldn't that be good health?
- Nope. That's security of wealth.
Damn it.
Here I was brought up to believe
that money can't buy you happiness.
I'm sorry. You've been misled.
Studies show that happiness in the over 45s
is overwhelmingly
tied to financial security.
I'm just talking about a comfortable
life in a nice little neighborhood.
Got you a piece of the
American pie, Sharon.
I live here by the beach.
Why else would anybody
want to live in this town?
You know, statistics point to
this being an inside job.
- Statistics?
- Yes.
Every series of human actions creates a pattern.
Now, I could show you a map
that would predict where 90% of the people
who develop heart disease will live in LA.
And I can tell you it's nowhere around here.
- It's science.
- Nice to meet you, Sharon.
It's nice to meet you too.
And you know we are well
within our rights to polygraph.
Every series of human actions creates a pattern.
The area you're looking at is seeing
219 robberies in the last 4 years.
Arthur, can you please remove
every robbery under 500k?
- Boom.
- CSI.
Go ahead.
Just here to listen.
Remove every robbery that
doesn't involve a courier,
delivery service or an armored vehicle.
Now, remove every robbery where there
was some type of violence used in a crime.
Lastly, remove every robbery where there
was some DNA or evidence left at the scene.
Boom.
As smart as that guy is, he
can't help but form a pattern.
He knows when the jewelers are
moving merchandise and when,
I believe by hacking their communications.
He doesn't use violence in every single case
he hits along the 101 freeway.
Last time was south.
I bet the next time is North.
What the fuck. Yo, give me the case.
What? What the fuck?
Hey You, hands up.
Get your fuckin' hands up.
Hey. Come here. Come here.
Get in front. Is there anyone in the back?
Is there anyone in the fuckin' back?
There's nobody in the back.
There's nobody there.
There's nobody in the back, huh?
There's nobody in the fuckin' back.
Shut up. Where's the key?
I don't have it.
- Where's the fuckin' key?
- That's outside.
It's in the car. It's in the car outside.
You're not playing games,
Okay? It's on my neck.
- I'll give it to you.
- Now.
Shut the baby up. What?
You open the fuckin' cabinet.
Don't work here. I don't work here.
Sit the fuck down.
Okay. Go around, unlock it. Now!
Don't you fucking look at me!
Put it on the bag!
Hurry up!
Come back around.
Take your ass back on the ground.
You come here.
Lay on here. Lay on down. Get the. On top.
Of the table.
It's okay. Shut up.
- Open the fuckin' door.
- Okay, okay, okay,
okay. It's easy, huh? Easy.
Remember I know what you look like.
Now you could take care of your baby.
Give us a room a minute.
Yeah, right.
- So what's your objective?
- What do you mean?
You just turned a bunch of
random robberies into a series.
You understand what that
means for the department, right?
- I understand that moving...
- Let me finish
two of your little examples.
There are cases that already have suspects.
Another one was closed by Fellner
six weeks ago. You understand?
Yeah, but he was wrong.
No, no, he wasn't wrong.
He went from red to black on the board.
That's never wrong.
You know what we don't do,
we don't reverse our
fucking clearance rates.
That's wrong.
But I know I'm right because
all of these are the same guy
and he doesn't let himself get caught.
Right? Right.
You're one brilliant factor
tying these all together.
Your guy's untraceable.
Come on.
You and I both know
- there's nothing here that's random.
- Stop talking.
Okay?
You got the lowest
clearance rate on the squad.
It's pulling everyone down. Me included.
What's the matter with you?
Used to be the...
You should have been sitting
in my seat by now, man.
Play the game.
Find a theory that works
for the whole building.
Thank you again. It's basically software
sales. Banks.
- Hey. Sorry I'm late.
- That's okay.
I crashed into someone and those
things take a long time to sort out.
- I'm guessing he. He stopped too fast. Huh?
- You know what? He did,
and it was fully his fault,
but I got another hot date out of it, so.
- Do you come here a lot?
- A couple times, yeah. couple times.
The. The Blanquette Devoe is supposed to be good.
Are you. Are you.
Are you in LA?
- I move around a lot.
- Do you?
Yeah. I prefer work.
- What is it you do?
- Basically?
Software development for Banks.
- Is it sales? It's not. Not very interesting.
- No, it's cool.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
I think maybe this wasn't a great idea.
You seem super great, and you're very.
But I honestly just don't see
us having all that much in common.
And I kind of have a rule
where if it doesn't feel right,
you just don't waste each
other's time.
But how do you know?
How do I know what?
That we won't have anything in common?
Uh. Well, I have no idea what Blanquette
Devoe is. I mean, I, I, I just.
I would never come to a place like this.
- Yeah, me neither.
- Really?
- I've never been here before.
- You've never been here?
Just thought it was a kind place
that people, you know, take people.
- I think it's Veal.
- What?
Oh. Oh. Veal.
Yeah, I. No, I would not eat that.
Definitely not. What would you eat?
I thought we loved each other.
Yeah, we do. But more in a force,
a habit kind of way. Right?
I mean, don't you want something
you can be excited about?
Something new?
You can get it.
- No. Fine. I don't need it.
- Pick it up.
No, I'm not picking it up.
- See you first.
- Fair.
Do you really want to know?
I'm going to move out at the weekend.
Now. You know what?
You stay. I'm move.
- Where are you gonna go?
- I, I, I may. Maybe I'll move to the beach.
- The beach? Are you serious?
- You're the least beach person I know.
- I'm way more beach than you are.
- bullshit
- How did your last relationship end?
- Work.
I had to. Had to move.
What motivates you?
Out of money, I guess.
What? Okay.
- Have you ever used handcuffs?
- Yeah.
If you had the option to press a button.
Oh. And start your life over,
- Would you press it?
- Yeah.
- You Would?
- Yeah, you?
- No.
- What's wrong?
- No, I mean, it's kind of
- What?
Sad. Okay, look,
I work for a publicist and we, we work
with musicians and, and actors and stuff.
And like, I swear to you, it doesn't matter
how much money they make.
It's never enough.
I'll know when I have enough.
- How?
- I have a number in mind.
But that was just enough to feel safe.
So you think maybe, Maybe we wanna...
- Meet up again?
- Yeah.
- Maybe.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
It happened in Santa Barbara.
A high end jeweler in
the central commercial district
a little after 10am the intruder was
captured by surveillance cameras,
but is said to aboard a motorcycle
helmet throughout the robbery.
This follows a string of high profile
robberies in Southern California.
Can we interview your witnesses?
They're not going to be able
to give you much.
The guy was wearing a motorcycle
helmet the whole time.
One of them shit their pants.
Literally shit in his pants.
Well, well, well.
101 robber.
There he is. Lou...
- Yeah. Something doesn't add up.
- I'm sorry, what?
Just...
What do you mean something
doesn't add up. Lou,
you said he was going to
hit north. Boom, he hits north.
Okay, we're barely a mile from a 101.
So the location fits the target, fits the M.O. it
fits, Lou, which I'm sorry, what you been done now?
Our guy never hurt anyone.
Oh, here's my champ.
What you got going?
Where's my account for the last job?
Why? What's the matter?
Santa Barbara was your last job. Oh,
Santa Barbara.
Yeah, I found it. I planned
it. I walked you through it.
And he said you didn't want to do it.
It wasn't yours to give away.
- You want to charge? Is that it?
- It's not about the fuckin' money.
Well, then what is it about?
It's about trust.
This happens again,
I think you and I are done.
You and I are done.
You're going to threaten me now?
Maybe you want to have a think
about where you'd be without me, huh?
Yeah,
I'll be here when you come back
with your tail between your legs.
Is this how you treat all your customers?
Or it's a special treatment for immigrants?
This is just a formality, Mr. Kassem.
If you have nothing to hide,
then you've got absolutely
nothing to worry about.
No, it's a formality.
You know what I object to is
not that I pay you to insure me
and you look for ways to
refuse to give what you owe.
It's that with this machine, you're
saying not only we think you're a thief,
but also we think you're a liar.
You know, Ms. Coombs,
those people you work for,
they're all kind parasites.
Are you also a parasite?
My guys planning something new.
I need you to find him and
I need you to follow him.
Here's someone he gets information from.
He's a Google guy or something.
You watch him.
- He'll show up.
- Then what?
You're not gonna rob the courier.
You let him do that and then you rob him
Stepmom. But sex.com.
Just the encryption location.
Follow the steps.
Yeah. It's funny what just
floats to the top of the old mind.
Thanks.
- White Mercedes GLE. Please.
- Yes, Ma'am. Let me right up.
- It's a cool car.
- Thanks.
Life's too short to drive boring cars, right?
- Elvis? He said that.
- All right.
- And what do you drive?
- See, that would be a gold Cadillac.
- Makes sense.
- You in the cars,
I like the ones with a bit of character.
- Would that be old ones or new ones?
- Today, an old one.
Today? I need to be in your line of work.
So what are we driving today?
If you can guess, I'll
give the keys to you.
Oh, be careful. I'm good at this.
- Yeah.
- Hmm
- All right.
- Okay, I'm gonna go with a Chevy Chevelle.
- Color?
- Racing green.
Right color.
Well, one out of two.
That's not bad.
Not bad at all.
That is a beautiful car though.
I underestimated you.
- Mike.
- Sharon.
- Nice to meet you, Mike.
- Nice to make you too.
Like I said, that's the last image we have.
Are you certain that we we don't pick
him up in the 101 in either direction?
Still certain.
And somewhere between that
turn and the 101, you switch cars.
Why are you so convinced he took the 101?
Hey, don't ask, man.
Look, there's 30 blocks
between there and the 101.
- Let's get looking.
- Are you serious?
- I'm serious.
- Lou, come on, man.
How's he gonna find him?
- The books come with the place, huh?
- Huh.
For someone who likes things, you
don't really have a lot of personal stuff.
No photos of family or...
- Do you have any?
- Photos?
- No. Family?
- Yeah.
- Someplace,
- Some place? Well, like in a drawer?
I don't know. We're just not really
that kind of family.
We really keep in touch. I don't know.
Do you have like brothers, sisters?
Mom, dad?
Yeah. Yeah. I don't know.
We. We didn't really have
a lot of stuff growing up.
And whatever we did have,
I didn't really keep any of it.
- What?
- Mystery man.
Hey, can I turn on some music?
Yeah, just a thing in the corner.
Do you have a favorite song?
No. Okay. I don't know why I would ask
why you would have a favorite song.
I suppose that's another black mark,
huh?
Do you. Do you listen to music or.
- Yeah, sometimes.
- Sometimes? You don't, do you?
- Come on.
- I can't dance.
Come on. Come on.
Come here. No photos, no music, no dancing.
Someone needs to teach
you how to be a human
♪ Cross the river to the Jersey side. ♪
I love that, they cheer for home
but no one does that for LA.
♪ On a Saturday night. ♪
♪ You know all my dreams come true  ♪
♪ When I'm walking
down the street with you ♪
♪ Sing. ♪
Yeah?
Yeah.
Scared?
Yeah. Maybe.
You're not gonna.
Do you want me to stay?
Yeah.
Good.
Hi, this is Mr. Stone.
I need a new apartment on the beach
available immediately.
Can I help you? Got delivery for Wilson.
I'm not expecting anything.
- It's got your name on it,
- Alright, Just leave it outside now.
Let's do that.
Leave it in the hall.
You going to tell me
what you gave him? Okay.
Tell me,
how many more of these garages
you going to make us do tonight, man?
Have you? What now what?
Sake, man.
Call forensics.
I wouldn't put it on my wall,
but I do love the sense of drama.
I think you can be confident
it's not going to lose its value.
The real question is,
how much do you love it?
Well, I love it. It'll go great
with the new chairs.
Really? You should want this guy glaring
down at us every time we have dinner.
- He's not glaring.
- He's glaring.
- I'm sure. And he's glaring.
- Really, he's just.
Excuse me. I'll be right with you.
Okay?
Sure. Thank you.
Wow. What a coincidence.
Hey. Sharon, right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah,
- Mike,
- That's it. Yeah. Good to see you.
So, do you collect art
like you do cars, Mike?
Not really,
but I like it. I like the sense of drama.
Hey, do you maybe want to get out of here?
Grab a drink or something?
I swear, man, divorced guys.
You always think you're
gonna move to the beach
and meet some hot surfer chick.
What you gonna do, take up surfing?
Nah, I wanna.
I'm thinking of doing the yoga.
The yoga?
Of course. You are.
- What kind?
- They got kinds?
Big time, man. They got hot yoga,
fast yoga, street yoga, Greek yoga.
Greek yoga. That last one might be food.
So you just wanna get laid?
Oh, man, I wanna get fit.
- Fitness,
- Please. Boo. Man, you.
- What's up?
- It's like a new car,
except for one microscopic speck of blood.
Is it enough to get DNA?
- Should be.
- Let me see.
- So I guess you work in the art world.
- Nope. Less glamorous.
I write insurance policies for
people who have more money
than they know what to do with.
You must know a lot
about what things are worth,
Hmm, too much.
But I also have to know a lot about the
people that own these things.
How do you mean?
You know, are you a thrill seeker?
Are you an alcoholic? Do you gamble?
Do you cheat on your partner?
You know, all those questions
that you can't ask,
but you obviously need to know the answers
to,
so you get real good at reading people.
What have you. What have you
read about me?
- Things you don't like or what?
- Nope.
No, did not say that.
Go on.
Okay. Well, you look like
a person who has secrets.
Your shirt's new or newly pressed,
which says you don't do your own laundry.
Or you're a bit OCD.
You're very groomed.
Your hair, your nails,
your $12,000 watch there.
Everything is just a little too perfect,
which tells me you have a lot of money
and a lot of time on your hands. Mike.
Got the clothes, the cars. You
can't seem to look me in the eye.
And I bet you didn't grow up with money.
How do you figure that?
Because people who grow up
in chaos crave order.
- You talking about me? Are you?
- Maybe both.
That hit too close to home?
No,
I have. I have a confession to make.
Really? I haven't finished my drinking.
This wasn't a coincidence,
us meeting again.
- Oh,
- I came here to talk to you.
You followed me?
I came here to make you
a business proposition.
You see, I know some things
about you too, Sharon.
Really? Like what?
You live alone. You're not
married, you never have been.
No children for to the same.
Same company for 11 years.
You're a VP when you should be a partner.
Who the fuck are you?
Just give me 30 seconds.
What I have to offer you, zero risk to you
and a huge upside to life changing upside.
No, that's okay.
What I do is I take certain pieces
of information from people like you.
And those ultra high value items
belonging to the rich guys you mentioned?
Well, I occasionally make them disappear.
But I do it in a way
that no one can trace it.
No one, one gets hurt. Except maybe
the shareholders of companies like yours.
Yeah. So you're a thief.
I get it. Let me tell you something,
Mike. I've gotten where
I've gotten through hard work.
I don't lie, I don't steal,
and I certainly don't cheat.
And I'm not about to start now.
Guys who work for you
think they're squeaky clean.
Mark, my partner in five years.
How do you think I know that?
I mean, you really think those
guys give a fuck about you?
Have a nice life, Mike.
If. If you change your mind, just
post a photo of a beach on Instagram
and I'll know to come find you.
Look, I don't know if
anybody's ever told you this,
but you live a fuck up life.
Take a moment to check in with yourself.
Check in and see where you may be
holding on to tension in this very moment.
Check in with your bread. You, your body,
Consciously breathe this tension out.
Let your heart open up
to the presence of love of all around
- Who you working for?
- All right.
Who are you working for?
Go away.
Well, you know, I'm.
I'm pretty much in between positions.
Right. Yeah. I'm looking to
pursue a career in hospitality.
- So. What did he tell you to do?
- He?
Yeah, what did he tell you to do?
- Your boyfriend?
- He.
- You tell you to follow me?
- Bro, I'm not gay.
Hey, stop fuckin' around. You follow me.
- Your boyfriend,
- Did he tell you follow me.
- I'm not gay.
- What he tell you to do?
- If I was gay,
- tell you to do?
Who are you working for?
Answer the fuckin' question.
- Don't touch me.
- Answer the fuckin' question.
Stop fuckin' Around.
- You want to kiss me?
- What he tell you?
- Do you want to kiss me?
- What he tell you to do?
Yeah. Okay. You tell him.
I see you again, you're both dead.
Understand?
Yeah. Yeah.
- You understand?
- Yeah. Okay.
Cool
Let go of your past.
Let go of your future.
Exist only in this moment.
Let's bring our left foot forward into our warrior
Let's reverse the warrior
Left elbow to left knee.
Raising our right hand.
Let's go down to the floor.
Raising our right hand to the sky.
Gaze toward the sun, the source of all life.
- What are you doing here, Detectives?
- What a coincidence.
Is it? This keeps happening to me.
All the lousy yoga joints in LA.
You either had a drastic change
of circumstance or you stalking me?
Just trying something new.
Trial separation.
Wonder if it's fun being
as smart as you. Sharon.
I'm sorry. I'm just not having a great week.
- This your first Yoga class?
- Pretty obvious, huh
Looks good on you.
That's a very kind lie.
Thank you.
- Hey, what's up?
- Townsend just took a call from Lafayette Jewelers.
He says there's someone hanging around
the outside of the store
who's a gone wrong.
- Sounds like our guy, Lou.
- Why would he be our guy?
He's a half mile from the 101.
And the owner says there's also
a suspicious car across the street.
- What's he driving?
- It's a dark one with blacked out windows.
Just like the one we found.
This could be our guy, Lou.
All right, I'm on my way. Make sure
Townsend doesn't beat you. There. Right.
The ground now. Don't get to.
No, no, no, no, no. Oh.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Does he have a weapon?
- No, I didn't see one.
- Stand up.
Do you think it's now,
- He's a fuckin' kid?
- Calling R.A.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey. Stand back. Hey.
- Get back.
- Wake up Townsend. What are you doing?
Cuff him.
Patrol got an officer involved shooting, Lou.
What? He says. He says it's his car. Which car?
The black one he says is his car rolling.
- What are you doing?
- He had a gun.
- What?
- He had a fucking gun.
- What are you talking about?
- Hey.
- What?
- He had a fucking gun. See for yourself.
Control 1479, we have five shots fired.
Suspect is down.
Suspect was armed with
a semi automatic handgun.
Let's see. ETA. All right.
Do you think maybe your little theory got
in everyone's head a little too much today?
You got about 30 minutes
before the shooting board arrives.
At this stage, you just need to get your
statement straight.
Yeah, he hadn't drunk.
You sure about that?
Gun was still in his bag.
Well, then we have a problem.
I don't want to bury anybody,
but I saw what I saw.
We have a problem because your statement
won't tally with Detective Townsend's.
Oh, yeah? Well, that's not exactly
a big surprise. Or your partners.
Tillman's account agrees with Townsend's.
Suspect was, gun in hand,
about to fire on a police officer.
And when times are difficult,
we pull together.
The three of you are suspended
until the investigation's concluded.
After which time you'll be welcomed back.
Unless one man should
choose a different path.
Congratulations are in order.
Madeline wrote her
first policy here at LNV.
She brought Monroe in on a state.
And she brought Monroe in on a
significant coverage on that wedding.
Beverly Wilshire. It's a great start. Madeline.
Congratulations. Oh my God.
Should have the mini V. Thank you.
Good start. Now let's keep the good work.
He actually wants to extend
cover to the wedding favors as well.
- Yeah.
- What's he giving him?
Diamonds for the bridal party. Around
12 karat each. So that's an extra 5.5 mil.
That's nice, but also high risk.
Make sure they have a good security plan.
Yeah, of course. I'm ready on it.
All right, I think that's it, everybody.
Madeline, good start.
- Sharon... Hold back to five real quick.
- Yeah, sure.
- You okay?
- Yeah, good,
Good. I finally
was able to wrangle the partners,
so I just wanted to fill you in.
Oh, good. Yeah. Great.
So the thinking is, given
the year that we had,
we're going to put a pin
in it until early next year.
We really want to get a clear financial picture
of everything before we make a decision.
- Okay? So hang tight.
- Really?
Yeah. Because it was my understanding
that we had a really good financial year.
I mean, not least thanks to
several of the policies that I wrote.
I mean, I can show you the numbers.
We looked at the numbers
and that's why come January,
we think you're going to be pretty happy.
But you got to hang in there until then.
Well, you said that last January.
Well, good things come
to those who wait, Sharon.
But I've been waiting.
I've been here for 11 years.
- I'm aware.
- Right.
And you made junior partner in 5
and senior in 7. So...
What's your question, Sharon?
My question is, if it's not gonna happen,
then I just would like to know that
so I can start considering myself
and maybe my clients, that's all.
Oh, you mean go to a competitor?
Well, I mean, I'm just saying.
You think one of our competitors
just gonna snatch you up
because you're gonna
present them the numbers?
I got a number for you, Sharon. 53.
It's not a good number for a
woman in this business, is it?
Because we know what those rich guys
are really buying and it's not 53.
Don't threaten me.
Got tillman's DNA match.
Which one's his desk?
I could take that.
There's a courier coming in from Antwerp.
He's carrying watches and gems for
a billionaires getting married.
Wedding fares.
with a value of 5.5 million.
- Where?
- The Beverly Wilshire.
What's the security setup?
We insist that armed security stay with our
courier until the transaction is completed.
And there's one more thing.
The buyer is paying cash for everything.
This way he doesn't pay tax and the
vendor doesn't have to declare to that IRS.
You're looking at $11 million in that room.
Of which I want three.
There separate security for the cash.
I don't know. We don't insure the cash.
So there could be.
Could be.
There's a lot of guns.
It's a busy location.
I'd say it's too risky.
Can I ask you something?
Have you ever done
a job for $11 million?
No, I haven't.
Isn't that what you guys call
walk away money?
Well, that's the thing
about walk away money,
is you gotta be able to walk away with it.
What made you change your mind anyway?
Maybe there comes a moment you realize
you don't have as much time
as you thought you had.
People keep running into Southland
unless you're on the 405 in South LA.
If you're headed southbound, you know
what I'm talking about there around shut down.
Now, CHP is calling that an animal hazard...
One third of the body's
lymphatic system is in the.
This is a new home.
You're trying to get into Hollywood.
You're thinking 101 southbound side right
there at Highland,
right near the Hollywood.
Ah. Can I help you? Good evening, Ma'am.
I'm Detective Lou Peznik from LAPD.
I got this address as a last known domicile
for a man by the name of James Davis.
Does that name mean anything to you?
Why would you be looking for him here?
You know Mr. Davis.
Why are you looking for him?
You have one forwarded message.
James, it's Ann. Sweetheart,
I don't know if this number works,
but I'd like to speak with you.
Will you call me if you can,
And it's all yours.
It's a pray.
Okay, boys, it's bedtime.
Come on, let's go.
Come on. Gentlemen, say good night.
Good night,
Why don't you leave your number?
Hello?
James? Hello?
Is everything okay?
A man came to look for you.
A policeman.
He's concerned about your safety.
Hello? James,
Jesus christ.
Hi. Listen, the courier.
When did he fly? What?
The courier you.
You were telling me about.
When he fly?
- I don't. I. I don't know. I. I don't.
- Days or weeks?
Well, the wedding is on a Sunday,
so. So I'm guessing Friday or Saturday.
Take this. Keep it on.
After we speak, take out the sim,
destroy it, then dispose of the phone.
Seriously? Isn't this what you want?
Hi. I was wondering if it'd be possible
to take a look at the wedding suite.
Let me see what I can show you.
Hold that place.
Yes. Yeah, I need you to get me the flight
number and security guard. I need a name.
- Everything I have.
- Shut the fuck up.
I'm not fuckin here for that. Okay,
You know what I'm here for?
Hey. What? You know what I want.
I have no idea what you want.
Don't. You gonna give me what you gave me?
I get to keep your face. Yeah,
you want to keep your face?
You tell me what you gave him. Okay.
Okay. Yeah, you're gonna tell me
what you gave him.
And when you're ready. Coming up into...
Can I buy you a coffee?
- or maybe a smoothie?
- Is everything okay?
Oh. What happened?
And what did you tell
the guy who attacked you?
I told him everything I told you.
Same as you told us, Mike?
Yeah.
Seeing as I told you all this. Is
that going to keep me out of jail?
You basically confessed to conspiracy
to commit gross larceny.
Yeah. We go official with this.
You're in black. It's ugly.
There's somewhere you
can stay for a few days.
Friend maybe?
Stay at my place.
Be safe.
Tell me more about this Mike.
Hey, how you doing? And I need to review
the evidence from a case from last week.
It's late. You know where it
is, cuz. I'm closing up in ten.
Oh, I'll just be. Won't be more
than five minutes.
- Five minutes?
- Yeah.
- All right. Thanks.
- Five minutes.
Thank you.
- You okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- I gotta go out of town for a while.
- Why?
The work thing. This. Opportunities come
up and I have to go.
- For how long?
- Not sure exactly.
You know, could be a while.
- Yeah.
- Can you do me a favor?
What's up? Can you just tell me the truth?
- That is the truth.
- Okay.
- And what is it that you do?
- I told you.
Hey, can I grab a drink?
Sure. Give me a second.
Look at me.
Look at me or I'm leaving.
Do you know how fucked up this is?
I mean,
I'm. I'm. I'm walking
around thinking that I.
Thinking about how much I like you.
And then I realize I don't even know you.
You haven't told me anything.
There are no photographs
Of your past. You seem to have
no family. You have no friends.
You have. There's. There's nothing.
I'm. I'm just asking you to wait for me.
Wait?
For what? For what?
No, seriously, for what?
For you to get to some magic
number? Don't patronize me
because you don't understand.
- It doesn't matter.
- What? Money?
Yeah. If you grow up, no money.
Then you don't have any choices.
And then shit happens.
Bad things come into your life.
- What kind of bad?
- Bad people.
Just ask me to wait a short time.
I'm not where I need to be yet. Okay.
I think you are.
Wow, look at you.
Pretending to be a capitalist.
Something like that. How'd you sleep? Good.
Yeah?
Have some coffee up there and some oat
milk in the fridge.
Thank you.
And make yourself at home.
Yeah, Sorry. I'm here for a pickup.
My phone's about to die.
You don't have a charge that I could
borrow, do you?
I do, buddy, but I'm.
Hands on the steering wheel. Bob.
Please don't hurt my family.
Start by handing me your phone.
Sign. Please be careful when
opening the overhead bins.
Items may have shifted
during flight and clear fallout.
You may continue to
use the cellular function.
Mr. Foster? Yes. Please follow me.
What's this about?
Foster.
Welcome.
Right. You're good to go.
Can I see some id?
Sure.
Thanks.
There you go. Good to go.
Flight okay, huh? Oh, yeah. Thanks.
Pretty used to it by now.
Come out this way a lot,
you know, a few times a year.
A lot of homeless here, huh?
Like to be dirt poor.
You wouldn't catch me
living on the sidewalk.
Sad saying.
Don't judge a man till you
walk the mile in his shoes.
I wore those shoes once.
They didn't suit me too well.
Say you're from. Not from here.
Louisiana. Bots.
Bunch of places. Moved around a lot
as a kid.
It's a nice car. You like cars? I prefer
the old American ones.
And what's yourself? I was a
kid, I dreamt about having a Mustang.
Like Steve McQueen. Yeah?
Yeah, Steve McQueen.
Funny guy your age.
Wouldn't normally know
who Steve McQueen is.
I grew up watching those movies.
What's your favorite? I say Bullet.
You know the Chases?
Yeah. Mine's Thomas Crown Affair.
The queen plays a high class thief.
I didn't catch that one.
Hey, Sharon.
Madeline. You don't have to do this.
You don't have to laugh
at his silly little jokes
or even act like you
like him or anything here.
Because that's what
I did for years and years.
And they told me exactly
what they're telling you.
That I was the Brightest
spark to ever be interviewed.
That they were waiting for somebody
like me to walk through that door.
They said that I would make
partner and that I would have equity,
that I would be set for life.
And then they dragged it on forever,
as if they were
HR problem. And for. There's
a protocol for that. And this is
You know what shut the fuck up.
You know what else?
They don't care how smart you are.
They don't care what you know or how
good you are. All you are to them is bait.
Bait to land the next big, fat rich fish
that these can't land for themselves.
Now, I don't know how many years that I'm
going to have left to offer since I'm 53,
but I do know that I'm not going to
give them to you.
Private security, visiting a
guest in The wedding suite.
It's fine. Go right ahead,
So, it's my first day. I'm supposed to be
on butler service.
Been here before? Yes, I have.
I take the next one, please, folks.
Hey, I forgot which
room I got to take this to.
It'll be on the ticket. Oh, first dab.
Don't know what I did with it. Dial 011.
Hey, I got drinks from Monroe.
I think they gave me the wrong
room number.
Mr. Monroe, I'm gonna call you back.
- Babe,
- That's yeah?
- Some guys here for you.
- Oh, okay, good. No, I want it as is
- Antwerp.
- That's right.
Okay, I gotta go.
Yeah, no, I gotta go.
Any problems?
- No. No, sir.
- No issues with customs?
Everyone, hands on your head
right now. No one needs to get hurt.
What the fuck do you think you're doing?
But you're on your knees facing the
wall, right now. You're the security guy.
He has a. He has a gun. Just.
He has a gun.
Hey, I'm not fuckin' around.
On your knees right now.
I'm not telling you again.
On your fuckin knees.
Please don't hurt me.
Briefcase on the table.
Hands in your head, then. kneel,
Let's go.
Now. Where's the cash flow, Monroe?
Cash?
What? There's no fuckin cash.
The cash you're using to
pay for the items in the case,
it's in the safe.
Where's the safe? Where's the safe?
- You know the code?
- No.
All right, Monroe, when I say so,
you're going to crawl over to the safe,
unlocked, but do not open it and
crawl back to where you are now.
- You understand?
- Yeah.
Move. Go. Jesus.
It's right here.
Stop messing around.
Come on.
Sorry. I'm sorry. Okay,
I got it. I'm not. There it
You fill this Bag up.
Security man open the briefcase.
- Come on, let's go.
- That's a combination.
That's okay. Nice and easy.
I take the diamonds out.
Jesus Christ,
man, is happening.
Hey, shut up.
Jesus, shut up, man. Stop talking.
Put the gun down.
I'm a police officer.
You're under arrest.
Put the gun down.
Second you pull that trigger, I pull mine.
You probably got a kid somewhere, right? For what?
For this crooked prick?
It's the last time I'm asking you,
put the gun down now. James,
I know all about you. And I know you
never hurt anyone before.
You're pointing a gun at a cop.
You're a cop? Then be a fucking cop.
Shut up the fucking guy.
Shoot him right now.
Shut up.
- Put the gun down.
- I'm not putting the gun down.
The last time I'm
asking you,
Put your gun down. Put your gun down.
Put the gun down.
Who the is he? He's a cop, kid.
Oh, you're a cop? Cop.
Put the gun down.
Hey, put it down.
You think I'm fuckin' playing?
Listen to me. Hey, listen to me,
Put the gun down.
I'm start counting. You
want blood in your cop hand?
Put it down.
- You want blood in your cop hand?
- You are a cop.
Why?
- Shut up.
- Shoot him.
Shut up.
Shoot him.
Fuck You. Yeah, you think I fucking play?
Fucking piece of shit.
Fuck you. Fuck you.
Just take what you came for,
Place the case towards me.
Place the fucking case toward me.
Take it.
- Don't fuckin' look at me.
- Not looking at you.
You are. You see my face, so
I need to put your gun down.
Put your gun down.
All right. Put the gun down. Gun down.
Put the gun down. Put the gun down.
Why? Put the gun down. Floor.
What? The gun down.
Put it down. You.
Oh.
My God.
Just look it.
He's dead.
Oh, he was gonna shoot you
Here's what you're going to do.
You're going to get in your car and
you're going to drive and never come back.
The money and the diamonds are still there.
There's the thief.
The 101 robbery.
I know.
I need to end this right now.
I'm gonna personally ensure that you do
time.
You're never gonna work ever again.
No, you're not.
You're gonna keep your money and
your stones.
When the cops show up here,
you're gonna listen to what I tell them.
And then you're gonna say what he said.
See, once they start investigating you
for the importation of Illegal
stones and tax evasion.
Then they really start digging.
So you better be squeaky fucking clean.
Is that what you want?
What the fuck is the matter with you?
I suggest you get all
that back in the safe.
Before my colleagues arrive.
Fuckin' coward.
This is Detective Lou Peznik, robbery division.
I'm at the Beverly Wilshire, room 1018. I need a RA unit.
I have two victims down, one KMA.
Another breathing.
Inhale.
Exhale.
You are safe.
You are calm.
You are exactly where you need to be.
Open yourself to the truth
of what's within you.
Don't hold back.
It's now time to slowly begin to bring
your awareness back into the physical body.
May you have a beautiful rest of your day.
- Namaste.
Hey. I came by your apartment.
Oh, yeah, I was away.
Yeah, I had a message.
Oh, yeah? I=I something for you.
Maybe. I don't open that in here.
Why? What is it?
Something nobody's looking for.
Said you have a message for me too.
This was sent to me.
- I don't know what that is.
- No.
Well. You think you'll be
coming back to yoga?
I don't know.
- Think I should?
- I think you should
- See you.
♪ Let the love set me free ♪
♪ Close to you is where I want to be ♪
♪ Let the set me free ♪
♪ Let the love set me free ♪
♪ Close to you is where I want to be ♪
♪ Let the love set me free... ♪
♪ I know you love me and ♪
♪ you fulfill all my needs ♪
♪ and no one comes between ♪
♪ to you I give glory ♪
♪ I know you love me and you fulfill all ♪
♪ my needs and no one comes between to you ♪
♪ I give glory to you I give glory ♪
♪ to you I give glory to you I ♪
♪ give glory. ♪
♪ Love set me free ♪
♪ Close to you is where I want to be ♪
♪ Let the love set me free ♪
♪ Let the last set me free ♪
♪ Close to you is where I want to be ♪
♪ Let the me free ♪
♪ not that love set me free ♪
♪ Close to you is where I want to be ♪
♪ Close to you is where I want to be. ♪
♪ Take your time to know ♪
♪ what you want ♪
♪ if you can use the mind control. ♪